Worlds will live, worlds will die and nothing will ever be the same.
Justice League: Crisis on Infinite Earths Part One is a animation,
science fiction, action film directed by Jeff Wamester.
Death is coming.
Worse than death: oblivion.
Not just for our Earth, but for everyone, everywhere, in every universe!
Against this ultimate destruction, the mysterious Monitor has
gathered the greatest team of Super Heroes ever assembled.
But what can the combined might of Superman, Wonder Woman, Batman, The Flash, Green Lantern and hundreds of Super
Heroes from multiple Earths even do to save all of reality from an unstoppable antimatter armageddon?!
The Flash / Barry Allen (voice), played by Matt Bomer.
Batman / Bruce Wayne (voice), played by Jensen Ackles.
Superman / Earth-2 Superman (voice), played by Darren Criss.
Supergirl / Harbinger (voice), played by Meg Donnelly.
Wonder Woman / Superwoman (voice), played by Stana Katic.
Green Arrow (voice), played by Jimmi Simpson.
Justice League: Crisis on Infinite Earths is a 2024 American animated superhero film trilogy featuring the DC Comics superhero team the Justice
League and based on the DC Comics storyline Crisis on Infinite Earths (1985–1986) written by Marv Wolfman and pencilled by George Pérez.
The films were directed by Jeff Wamester from a script by Jim Krieg.
They are the 54th, 55th, and 56th films of the DC
Universe Animated Original Movies.
They are the eighth, ninth, and tenth (and final) installments in the second phase of the DC
Animated Movie Universe, as well as the 23rd, 24th, and 25th (and final) films overall.
Justice League: Crisis on Infinite Earths – Part
One was released on January 9, 2024.
Part Two was released on April 23, and Part Three was released on July 16.
The films were dedicated to comic artist George Pérez who died on May 6, 2022, and
longtime Batman actor Kevin Conroy who died later that same year on November 10.
The film explores themes of superhero, villain, end of the
world, based on graphic novel, superhero team.
The tone is thought_provoking.